ILGWU. David Melman papers, 5780/152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- General Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Uretek Incorporated, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Homework: Local Paper Articles and Other Press Reports, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Homework: Letters, Clippings etc., 1986 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Pro-Homework Press Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Homework, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Homework: House Testimony, 1981-1986 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Stedman Column, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Deva, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Articles Sent to Homework Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1980-1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Articles Sent to Homework Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1980-1987 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Zoning and Development, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Kay Windsor, Incorporated: Master Agreement, 1967-1973 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Kay Windsor, Incorporated: Audit, 1968-1972 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Kay Windsor, Incorporated: Ballston, Cameo, Poultney (Supplemental Agreement, 1970-1973 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Kay Windsor, Incorporated: Supplemental Agreement for Reynolds Manufacturing Company, Taber Manufacturing Company, 1970-1973 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Kay Windsor, Incorporated: Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Kay Windsor, Incorporated: Negotiations, 1970-1974 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Kay Windsor, Incorporated, 1965-1973 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: General [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1987 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: General [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1987 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation/Calvin Klein, Incorporated: Audit Correspondence, 1979-1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Calvin Klein, Incorporated: Audit Bills, 1985-1993 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- UNITE New York State Council, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- UNITE Legislative Agenda, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- UNITE: Trade, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- UNITE Ad Campaign, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- UNITE: Committees and Task Forces, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- UNITE Paraphernalia, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- United Food and Commercial Workers, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- United Garment Workers, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- United Paperworkers International Union, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- United Steel Workers of America, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- United Textile Workers, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- University of North Carolina Press, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- White House Apparel Industry Task Force, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Task Force on Warehouse Organizing, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Vestar Capital Partners, 1988-1995 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Window, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Women's Outerwear, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Workers Benefits Committee, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Wrist Injuries, 1991-1993 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Zensen, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Gus Tyler's Party, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Uniform Project, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Union Administration, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Union Administration, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Union Label Department, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Union Square Sculpture, 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- UMWA, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Constitution, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- UNITE Elections, 1992-1995 (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Incorporated [folder 1 of 3], 1987-1991 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Incorporated [folder 2 of 3], 1987-1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Incorporated [folder 3 of 3], 1987-1991 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- UNITE Mission Statement, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Incorporated: Pennsylvania, Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1992 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Incorporated: Pennsylvania, Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1992 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Leslie Fay Companies, Incorporated: Sassco, Correspondence, 1983-1996 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: Withdrawal Liability, 1982-1984 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Calvin Klein: Wellford Agreement, 1992-1995 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: Saybrook Classics, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Tococo, Incorporated: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation: South Carolina Shops, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Puritan Fashions Corporation, Calvin Klein: Waterboro- Chatham Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Puritan Fashions/Calvin Klein: Paul Modes Correspondence, 1980-1994 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Calvin Klein: Arbitrators, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Puritan Fashions/Calvin Klein: Arbitration Correspondence, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Calvin Klein, Incorporated: Securities Report, 1981-1991 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Puritan Fashions/Calvin Klein: Company Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Puritan Fashions/Calvin Klein: Centerfold Correspondence [folder 1 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Puritan Fashions/Calvin Klein: Centerfold Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1980-1984 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- JH Collectibles: Background [folder 1 of 2], 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- JH Collectibles: Background [folder 2 of 2], 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Junior House Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1987-1997 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Junior House Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1987-1997 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- JH Collectibles: Correspondence, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Just Cynthia, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Junior House Clippings, 1988-1997 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Junior House Agreement, 1994-1997 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- JH Collectibles, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Kentucky Apparel, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- S. Klein, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- K-Mart, 1993-1997 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Kolcraft, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Koret of California, 1989-2001 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Kors, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Kobra International (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Tinkleman, Larry, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Los Angeles: Sewing With Dignity, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Le Coq Sportif, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Leon Levin Sons, Incorporated, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Levi Strauss, 1993-1997 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Lilli Ann Corporation, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Marc Jacobs, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Marshall's Incorporated, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Master Agreement Cover Sheets, 1988-1991 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Master Agreement, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Master Agreement Monthly Audit, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Master Apparel Corporation Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Isaac Mizrahi and Company, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Mossimo, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Mr. Jax, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Mulberry, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 32)
- New Jersey Headwear Corporation, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 33)
- New York Department Stores, 1984-1990 (Box 45, Folder 34)
- Nicole Miller, 1989-1992 (Box 45, Folder 35)
- Organizing Reports: Departments of Organization and Field Services, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 36)
- Organizing Reports: New York City Locals, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Organizing Reports: Regions, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 38)
- Organizing, 1987-1999 (Box 45, Folder 39)
- Oscar De La Renta: Apparel Group International, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Party Rental, Limited, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Paulette Fashions, 1982-1988 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Saha, 1988-1996 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Peerless, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Pendleton, 1995-1997 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Phelps-Dodge, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Plaid Clothing Group Incorporated, 1993-1995 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Plaid Clothing Group, Incorporated, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Plaid Clothing Group, Incorporated: Background, 1993-1996 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- El Ponce De Leon Convalescent Center, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Quartet Fashions, 1993-1995 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- ILGWU: Rainfair with Local 187, 1991-1995 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- REO Originals/VLP Corporation, 1990-1994 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Robby Len Industries, Incorporated, 1991-1994 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Robby Len Industries, Incorporated: Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Robyn Meridith, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Roxanne Swimsuit Division, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Salant Corporation, 1990-1999 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- San Francisco Knitworks, Incorporated, 1995-1998 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Schottenstein, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Sew-Sew/G.P. Fashions, 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Sharilove Fashions, Incorporated, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Sidney Bernstein and Son Lingerie, Incorporated, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Shoulder Pads, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Smoler Brothers Correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Sorrento Coats, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Spike Lee's Sportswear Company, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- South Jersey, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- St. John Knits, Incorporated, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Stonehenge, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Sun Apparel, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Swimwear Industry, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Tahari, Limited, 1994-2000 (Box 46, Folder 34)
- Takihyo, 1990-1994 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- LM-2 [folder 1 of 2], 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- LM-2 [folder 2 of 2], 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Minutes: Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board Minutes: Meetings, 1986-1989 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board Minutes: Meetings, 1986-1989 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board Minutes: Meetings, 1986-1989 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1991-1994 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Bill, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board: Guest Arrangements, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board: Attachments, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board: Back-Up, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board: Meetings, Guest Information, 1989-1992 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board: Meeting, Guest Arrangements, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board: Meetings, Menus, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangement, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board: Bill, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- General Executive Board: Guest Arrangements, 1991-1993 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Hotel Arrangements, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board: Guest Arrangements, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board: Topics, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board: Guest Arrangements, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board: Meeting, Agenda, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board: Meeting, Guest Arrangements, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board: Meeting, Hotel Arrangements, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Hotels, 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board: Guest Arrangements, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board: Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board: Topics, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  Spanish, Chinese
- General Executive Board: Guests Arrangements, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board: Hotel Arrangements, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board: Agenda, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board: Guest Arrangements, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Tommy Hilfiger, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- The Limited, 1987-1998 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- The Limited: Background, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- TJX: Las Vegas Nevada, Agreement, 1989-1996 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- TJ Maxx, 1994-1998 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- TJ Maxx: Clippings, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- TJ Maxx Contract Comparison, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Trueform, 1989-1997 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Trueform Liquidated Damages Bill, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Trigere, Pauline, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- John H. Van Patten Company, Incorporated, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- VF Corporation, 1995-1998 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Victoria Pleating and Embroidery, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- VT Fashions (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Wal-Mart, 1997-1998 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Wash Great, Incorporated, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- White Stag, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Wicker Park Bill, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Wicker Park, L.P.: Bankruptcy, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Wicker Park Industries, Incorporated: Sale of Assets Documents, 1986-1990 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Wicker Park, L.P.: Master Agreement [folder 1 of 2], 1991-1994 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Wicker Park, L.P.: Master Agreement [folder 2 of 2], 1991-1994 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Wilke-Rodriguez, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Willmar Fashions, Incorporated, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Kay Windsor, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Windsor Knitting Mills, 1992-1995 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Winston Mills/Puritan Fashions, 1980-1988 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Xerox, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Country Miss, Incorporated, 1988-1992 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Cookeville Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Easton Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Glasgow Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Bristol Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Bristol Virginia, Problem, 1993-1995 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Country Miss, Incorporated, 1991-1993 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Walterboro Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Bristal, Virginia Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Carrollton Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Termination Notices, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Cookeville Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Easton Agreement, 1991-1993 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement, 1988-1994 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Original Signed Agreements, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1989 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1989 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Agreement, 1981-1984 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Miscellaneous Undated Material, 1983-1987 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Bristol, Virginia Agreement, 1977-1985 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Fairfield, Virginia Agreement, 1979-1982 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Cookeville Agreements, 1973-1985 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Bristol, Virginia Agreement, 1985-1988 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Carrollton, North Carolina Agreement, 1983-1986 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Cookeville, Tennessee Agreement, 1985-1988 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement, 1985-1988 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Agreement, Original Signed Copies, 1985-1988 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Arbitrations, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Job Training and Research Corporation, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement Chart, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Clipping, 1980-1994 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: 1992 Master Agreement Negotiation, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Restructuring, 1988-1990 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Contract Termination Notices, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Financial Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Audit Bills [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1993 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Audit Bills [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1993 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Bristol, Virginia, 1978-1986 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Bristol Complaints, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Carrollton Correspondence, 1978-1990 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Cookeville Correspondence, 1978-1986 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Easton Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Glasgow, Kentucky Correspondence, 1955-1994 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Bristol, Virginia Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Carrollton, Alabama Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Cookeville, Tennessee Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Glasgow, Kentucky Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement, Unsigned Drafts, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Master Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: New York City Sample Room Contract, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: New York City Sample Room Contract, 1988-1993 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Walterboro, North Carolina Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Country Miss, Incorporated: Agreements, Original Signed Copies, 1988-1991 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Creditors Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Credit Committee Background, 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Deloitte and Touche LLP Bill, 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Eminent Domain, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Forty Hours, 1987-1991 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Import Quotas Violations, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Industrial Union Department, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Keilin and Bloom, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Labor Management Committee [folder 1 of 3], 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Labor Management Committee [folder 2 of 3], 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Labor Management Committee [folder 3 of 3], 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Pennsylvania, 1993-1994 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Politicians, 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Potential Buyer, 1992-1994 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Rally, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Retailers Boycott, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Other Union Support, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Creditors Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Stakeholders [folder 1 of 2], 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Stakeholders [folder 2 of 2], 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Women's and Religious Outreach, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Mary Ann Restivo, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Spitalnick with Local 169, ACTWU, 1987-1990 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Shapely Agreement, 1982-1995 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Summit Sportswear Company, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Morrow, Georgia Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Morrow, Georgia Agreement, 1979-1994 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Next Day Agreement, 1992-1994 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Sam Elias, Non-Stop, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Sam Elias: Non Stop, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Overton Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Boston Agreement, 1982-1994 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Julie I and II Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Kathryn Conover Agreement, 1983-1985 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- The Leslie Fay Companies Incorporated: Lincolnton, North Carolina Agreement, 1976-1982 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Local 153: New Agreement, 1988-1991 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Johnathan Logan: Shutdown, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- R&K: Misty Harbor, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Drug Testing: Misty Harbor, 1988-1990 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- February Meeting: Drug Testing, 1988-1990 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Johnathan Logan: Drug Policy, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- United Merchants and Manufacturers, Incorporated, 1990-1992 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Jonathan Logan, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- United Merchants and Manufacturers, Incorporated: Villager, R&K, 1981-1990 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- United Merchants and Manufacturers, Incorporated [folder 1 of 2], 1991 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- United Merchants and Manufacturers, Incorporated [folder 2 of 2], 1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Local 153, 1987-1993 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Local 153, 1988-1994 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Berman, Jean: Local 153, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Lamey, Valerie: Local 153, 1978-1990 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Local 153: Shugalter, Clara, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Christiano, Alice, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Local 153: Hassan, Annette, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Local 153, 1985-1991 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Local 153: Negotiations, 1988 Contract, 1984-1988 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Local 153: Contract Negotiations, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Local 153: Beverly Downs, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Local 153: Solomon, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Local 153: Fair Employment (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Local 153: Non-discrimination, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Local 153: Negotiations, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Local 153: Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Carmen Laureano, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Local 153: Lillian Miller-Reid, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Local 153: Kitty Krupat, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Local 153: Agreement, 1991-1994 (Box 56, Folder 25)